dormsmart.com 2017-03-02

# DormSmart.com Privacy Policy & Security

At DormSmart.com, we value your trust. Therefore, we have created this privacy policy because we want you to know how we collect, use and protect information about our online guests.

What information does DormSmart.com collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, subscribe to our mailing list(s), respond to a survey or fill out a form. In addition, we may collect information you submit about other people for the purpose of fulfilling an order, for example, the name and address of a gift recipient. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as optional.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail. This practice, called "phishing", is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond.

What does DormSmart.com use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To protect the security and integrity of our site for our shoppers. (Note: Once you leave our website, we DO NOT track you.)

To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. **(Note** : If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses such as Google Adwords.

 **How do we use Google AdWords?**

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites, including Google, to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to this website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/). In other words, you can opt out.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. ( **Note** : This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.)

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their "My Account" section and making the desired changes or [emailing us](mailto:customerservice@dormsmart.com?subject=Account%20Change%20Request).

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Store Policies / Terms & Conditions

Please visit our [Store Policies](http://www.dormsmart.com/DormSmart-Store-Policies-18.html) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on May 8, 2015.

Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

DormSmart.com, L.L.C.  
609 SW 8th Street, Suite 600  
Bentonville, AR 72712  
United States  
www.dormsmart.com  
877-616-3676

Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * Federal Trade Commission Fair
  * California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Privacy Alliance
  * Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
